A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Fellowships and Training Programs, RG 4 FA1402
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council records, Fellowships and Training Programs, RG 4
1971-2005
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council
FA1402
36.1 Cubic Feet 95 letter document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Biographical / Historical
The Asian Cultural Council is a publicly supported not for profit 501(c)(3) established in 1980 to support cultural exchange between Asia and the United States. The Council carries forward the mission of the Asian Cultural Program of the JDR 3rd Fund, which had been created by JDR 3rd in 1963 and was officially dissolved in July 1979.
The Asian Cultural Council maintains offices in New York, Hong Kong, Manila (Philippines), Taipei (Taiwan) and Tokyo. ACC affiliation with the Rockefeller Brothers Fund began in 1991, enabling the Council to reduce administrative overhead and devote a larger percentage of its funds directly to grants and program development.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Asian Cultural Council records were donated to the RAC in 2010.
Other Finding Aids
Other available findig aids describing the Asian Cultural Council records include:
FA427 Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1
FA1400 Asian Cultural Council records, Conferences, Festivals and Seminars RG 2
FA1401 Asian Cultural Council records, Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture RG 3
FA1402 Asian Cultural Council records, Fellowships and Training Programs, RG 4
FA1403 Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5
Scope and Contents
Record Group 4 primarily consists of Fellowship and Training Program administration records and supporting documentation.
Arrangement
Record Group 4 Fellowships and Training Programs is arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP)
Series 2: Indo-American Fellowship Program (IAFP)
Series 3: Indonesian Museum Training Program (IMTP)
Series 4: Japan-United States Museum Professional Exchange Program (JUMP)
Series 5: Triangle Arts Program (TAP)
Series 6: Japan-United States Arts Program (JUSAP)
Series 7: Asian Fellowships
Series 8: Philippines Fellows
Series 9: Taipei Fellows
Series 10: Taiwan Dance Fellowship Program
Series 11: Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program
Series 12: Taiwan Fellowship Program
- Fellowships and Training Programs, 1971-2005; 4
  - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), 1989-2002; 1
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 317, Folder 1-2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), General Correspondence, 1993 (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), General Correspondence, 1994 (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1989 Spring (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1990 Spring (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1991 Spring (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1992 Spring (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1993 Spring (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1994 Spring (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1995 Spring (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1996 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1996 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, C-L, 1997 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, M-Z, 1997 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1998 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 1999 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 2000 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 2001 Spring (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 2001 Spring (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Hong Kong Arts Program (HKAP), Declinations, 2002 Spring (Box 329, Folder 1)
  - Indo-American Fellowship Program (IAFP), 1976-1995; 2
    - IAFP, Harris, Marvin, 1976-1977 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, Robinson, Marguerite S., 1976-1977 (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, Keightley, Willard O., 1976-1977 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, Shaffer, Jim G., 1976-1977 (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, Salomon, Richard G., 1976-1977 (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, Dahiya, Ram C., 1976-1977 (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, Catlin, Amy Ruth, 1976-1977 (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, Harrington, Joseph J., 1976-1977 (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, Larson, Gerald J., 1976-1977 (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, Bhattarcharji, Somdev, 1977-1978 (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, Hartjen, Clayton A., 1977-1978 (Box 331, Folder 3-4)
    - IAFP, Green, Mark, 1977-1978 (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, Henry, Edward O., 1977-1978 (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, Helstein, Melvyn, 1977-1978 (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, Kroopnick, Peter, 1977-1978 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Brunner, Christopher (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, Brittenham, Gary, 1977-1978 (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, Freed, Ruth S., 1977-1978 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, Alternate Candidates, 1977-1978 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, Odend?hal, Stewart, 1977-1978 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, Clark Worswick, 1977-1978 (Box 332, Folder 7)
    - LT: IAFP, Babb, Lawrence, 1978-1979 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - LT: IAFP, Gangong, Richard (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Goreen, Leonard, LT (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Horowitz, Bernard (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - LT: IAFP, Barnow, Eric, 1978-1979 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, 1976-1977 (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - IAFP Operations, Selection, 1976-1977 (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - IAFP Operations, Screening, 1976-1977 (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - IAFP, Follow-Up (Box 333, Folder 9)
    - Sub-Commission: IAFP, Placement of Indian Fellows, 1976-1977 (Box 333, Folder 10)
    - IAFP, Non Applicant Survey, 1977-1978 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, Operations, Selections, 1977-1978 (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, Abstracts from Fellows for NSF-SI Prop., 1977-1978 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, Requests for Information, Fellowships and Funding, 1977-1979 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, Operations, Distributions of Announcements, 1977-1978 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, Operations, Announcement: Instruments and Information for Applicants, 1977-1978 (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, Operations, Screening, 1977-1978 (Box 334, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, Placement of Indian Fellows, 1977-1978 (Box 334, Folder 8)
    - IAFP, Acceptance & Placement of American Fellows, 1977-1978 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - IAFP, Announcement-Distribution, 1976-1977 (Box 334, Folder 10)
    - IAFP Operations, Principal Candidates, 1977-1978 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - IAFP Operations (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - IAFP Operations, Screening, 1978-1979 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, Administrative Procedures (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - IAFP Operations, Selection Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Board of Foreign Scholarships, 1978 September 7-8 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, Alternate Candidates, 1978-1979 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - IAFP (Indians), 1978-1979 (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Sub-Commission: IAFP, Acceptance-Placement of American Fellows by Indian Side, 1976-1977 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, Kohin, Roger P., 1976-1977 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - LT IAFP, Jain, Subodh, 1978-1979 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - LT IAFP, Lukacs, John, 1978-1979 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - LT IAFP, Nichter, Mark, 1978-1979 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - LT IAFP, Phinney, Robert, 1978-1979 (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - LT IAFP, Raff, Martin, 1978-1979 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - LT IAFP, Schomer, Karine, 1978-1979 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - LT IAFP, Wilkes, Hilbert, 1978-1979 (Box 336, Folder 9)
    - LT IAFP, Zide, Norman, 1978-1979 (Box 336, Folder 10)
    - ST IAFP, Abu-Lughod, Janet, 1978-1979 (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - ST IAFP, Eck, Diana, 1978-1979 (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - ST IAFP, Eyring, Edward, 1978-1979 (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - ST IAFP, Fenn, John Bennett, 1978-1979 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - ST IAFP, Juergensmeyer, Mark, 1978-1979 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - ST IAFP, Schechner, Richard, 1978-1979 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - ST IAFP, Scholberg, Henry, 1978-1979 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - ST IAFP, Zelinsky, David, 1978-1979 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - ST IAFP, Auffenberg, Walter, 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - ST IAFP, Brown, Leon, 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - ST IAFP, Ericson, Jonathon, 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - ST IAFP, Guillet, David W., 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 10)
    - ST IAFP, Handler, Joel (Withdrew 1979-1980) (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - ST IAFP, Nakamura, Royden, 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 12)
    - ST IAFP, Noe, Samuel V., Jr., 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 13)
    - ST IAFP, Powers, Jean D., 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 14)
    - ST IAFP, Powers, Thomas, 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 15)
    - LT IAFP, Brereton, Joel (Withdrew), 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 16)
    - LT IAFP, Brown, Carolyn, 1979-1980 (Box 337, Folder 17)
    - LT IAFP, Cort, Louise, 1979-1980 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - LT IAFP, duBois, Ron, 1979-1980 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - LT IAFP, Dahringer, Lee, 1979-1980 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - LT IAFP, Fooden, Jack, 1979-1980 (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - LT IAFP, Frye, Nelson, 1979-1980 (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - LT IAFP, Herring, Ronald, 1979-1980 (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - LT IAFP, Norr, James L., 1979-1980 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - LT IAFP, Oliveria, Forrest L. (Withdrew), 1979-1980 (Box 338, Folder 8)
    - LT IAFP, Rice, Marion, 1979-1980 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - LT IAFP, Poulos, John W., 1979-1980 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - LT IAFP, Stein, Achva B., 1979-1980 (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - LT IAFP, Stein, Joel D., 1979-1980 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - LT IAFP, Weeks, Clair H., 1979-1980 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - ST IAFP, Anderson, Lawrence, 1978-1979 (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - LT IAFP, Lintault, J. Jean, 1979-1980 (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, General Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Indo-US American Fellowship Program, 1979-1980 (Box 339, Folder 9)
    - Long and Short Term Fellowships, Award Letters and Information (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - IAFP, Indian Fellows, 1979-1980 (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, Indians to US, 1979-1980 (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, 1979-1980 (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - IAFP Operations, Announcements, 1979-1980 (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, Selection Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 340, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, Screening Selection, 1979-1980 (Box 340, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, Alternates, Short Term, 1979-1980 (Box 340, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, Alternates, Long Term, 1979-1980 (Box 340, Folder 8)
    - IAFP, Terms and Conditions and Gomes Memorandum, Awards Enclosed, 1979-1980 (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - IAFP Operations, Future of IAFP (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - IAFP, Requests for Information, Fellowships and Funding, 1980-1981 (Box 340, Folder 11)
    - ST IAFP, Brigham, Raymond D., 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - ST IAFP, Beuchat, Larry R., 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - ST IAFP, Davis, Fred, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - ST IAFP, Goos, Roger D., 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - ST IAFP, Girdany, Bertram (Withdrawn), 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - ST IAFP, Handler, Joel (Withdrawn), 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 6)
    - ST IAFP, Richards, James H., 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 7)
    - ST IAFP, Sreevasam, Elsa Marie, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 8)
    - ST IAFP, Stelmach, George, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 9)
    - ST IAFP,Tsubaki, Andrew, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 10)
    - LT IAFP, Donegan, Patricia, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 11)
    - LT IAFP, Eames, Edwin, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 12)
    - LT IAFP, Everson, Norma Doris, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 13)
    - LT IAFP, Grew, Edward, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 14)
    - LT IAFP, Hargraves, Robert, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 15)
    - LT IAFP, Knight, Roderic C., 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 16)
    - LT IAFP, Libersat, Murray, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 17)
    - LT IAFP, Langenbach, Richard, 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 18)
    - LT IAFP, Lopez, David E., 1980-1981 (Box 341, Folder 19)
    - LT IAFP, McGovern, Terry, 1980-1981 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - LT IAFP, Oliveria, Forrest L., 1980-1981 (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - LT IAFP, Singer, Norman J., 1980-1981 (Box 342, Folder 3)
    - LT IAFP, Tuttle, T. Temple, 1980-1981 (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - LT IAFP, Weinstein, Brian, 1980-1981 (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - LT IAFP, Westfall, Carol, 1980-1981 (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - Ethnicity Seminar: Logistics (Box 342, Folder 7)
    - The TAJ Express (Box 342, Folder 8)
    - Sub-Commission Programs, Puppets, 1979-1980 (Box 342, Folder 9)
    - Kuttyattum Troupe, Wenner Gren Foundation (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Trinity Square Repertory Company (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - Trienenale in Delhi, 1982 (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, Indians to USA, 1980-1981 (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, 1980-1981 (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, Short Term & Long Term Fellows, 1980-1981 (Box 343, Folder 6)
    - LT IAFP, Alternates, 1980-1981 (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - ST IAFP, Alternates, 1980-1981 (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - IAFP, Selection Process, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - ST IAFP, Alternates, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - LT IAFP, Alternates, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - LT IAFP, ARRUCCI, John, Smithsonian, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - LT IAFP, Dannhaeuser, Norbert, NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 6)
    - LT IAFP, Edmundson, Wade C., Smithsonian, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - LT IAFP, Gilman, Robert, NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - LT IAFP, Hiltebeital, Alfred, Smithsonian, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 9)
    - ST IAFP, Howard, James D., NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 10)
    - LT IAFP, Nettl, Bruno, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 11)
    - LT IAFP, Ray, Davis E., Smithsonian, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 12)
    - LT IAFP, Emigh, John S., Smithsonian, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 13)
    - ST IAFP, Reed, Robert R., Smithsonian, 1981-1982 (Box 344, Folder 14)
    - ST IAFP, Hagstad, Harry, NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - ST IAFP, Heller, Hoarace C., NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 2)
    - ST IAFP, Howard, James D., NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 3)
    - ST IAFP, Krislov, Joseph, Smithsonian, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 4)
    - ST IAFP, Lyovin, Anatole, Smithsonian, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 5)
    - ST IAFP, Rhodes, Lucille R., 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 6)
    - LT IAFP, Ryan, Joseph S., Jr., 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 7)
    - LT IAFP, Schaumberg, Gene David, NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 8)
    - LT IAFP, Wallach, Brett, NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 9)
    - ST IAFP, Bonney, William, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 10)
    - ST IAFP, Epstein, William, NSP, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 11)
    - ST IAFP, Gerson, Charles, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 12)
    - ST IAFP, Girdany, Bertram, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 13)
    - ST IAFP, Sakata, Hiromi, Smithsonian, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 14)
    - ST IAFP, Schreiber, Ralph W, NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 15)
    - ST IAFP, Selden, Richard, NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 16)
    - ST IAFP, Smith, Norman D., NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 17)
    - ST IAFP, Staelin, Charles, NSF, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 18)
    - ST IAFP, Watson, Geoffrey Stuart, 1981-1982 (Box 345, Folder 19)
    - ST IAFP, Woodward, James, 1981-1982 (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - Sub-Commission: "Methods in History" Joint Seminar (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - Seminars, Ethnicity (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Ethnicity Seminar Follow-up (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - Papers, Indians, Ethnicity Seminar (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Papers, Americans, Ethnicity Seminar (Box 347, Folder 1)
    - Joint Seminars: Ethnicity (II) (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - LT IAFP, Barkan, Joel D., NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 347, Folder 3)
    - LT IAFP, Barnum, David, 1983-1984 (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - LT IAFP, Buckley, Suzanne, 1983-1984 (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - LT IAFP, Caplan, Robert D., 1983-1984 (Box 347, Folder 6)
    - LT IAFP, Conlon, Joan C., 1983-1984 (Box 347, Folder 7)
    - LT IAFP, Freeman, Daniel H., Jr., NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 347, Folder 8)
    - LT IAFP, Groselose, Barbara D., 1983-1984 (Box 347, Folder 9)
    - LT IAFP, Iyer, Hariharaiyer, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 347, Folder 10)
    - LT IAFP, Kliks, Michael, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - LT IAFP, Lang, Jon, 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - LT IAFP, Matis, James, 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - LT IAFP, Naroll, Maud, 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 4)
    - LT IAFP, Manuel, Oliver K., 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 5)
    - LT IAFP, Morningstar, Patricia, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 6)
    - LT IAFP, O'Hara, Mary L., 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 7)
    - LT IAFP, Rose, Susan, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 8)
    - LT IAFP, Styer, Robert A., NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 9)
    - LT IAFP, Swiderski, Richard, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 10)
    - ST IAFP, Weiss, James, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 348, Folder 11)
    - ST IAFP, Wolinsky, Ira, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, 1983-1984 (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, Indian Scholars, 1983-1984 (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, Selection of American Fellows, 1983-1984 (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - LT IAFP, Alternates, 1983-1984 (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - ST IAFP, Alternates, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 350, Folder 1)
    - ST IAFP, Alternates, 1983-1984 (Box 350, Folder 2)
    - LT IAFP, Alternates, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 350, Folder 3)
    - ST IAFP, Canipe, Nancy K., 1983-1984 (Box 350, Folder 4)
    - ST IAFP, Foss, Clive, 1983-1984 (Box 350, Folder 5)
    - ST IAFP, Herz, Norman, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 351, Folder 1)
    - ST IAFP, Hooper, Peter, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 351, Folder 2)
    - ST IAFP, Hoffstein, Jeffery, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 351, Folder 3)
    - ST IAFP, Malville, John McKim, NSF, 1983-1984 (Box 351, Folder 4)
    - LT IAFP, Alternates, S. I., 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folder 5)
    - ST IAFP, Alternates, S.I., 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folder 6)
    - ST IAFP, Alternates, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, Selection Process, 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folder 8)
    - IAFP, Indian Grantees, 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folder 9)
    - IAFP, American Candidates, 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folder 10)
    - ST IAFP, Agenbroad, James, Smithsonian (SI), 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folder 11)
    - ST IAFP, Bloom, David, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folder 12)
    - ST IAFP, Bonney, William, SI, 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folder 13)
    - ST IAFP, Campbell, Douglas, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 351, Folder 14)
    - ST IAFP, Candland, Douglas, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - ST IAFP, Barnum, David, SI, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 2)
    - LT IAFP, Cell, John, SI, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 3)
    - LT IAFP, Du Puy, Karl, SI, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - ST IAFP, Fleckenstein, Joan P., Deceased, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 5)
    - LT IAFP, Gaddis, Philip K., NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 6)
    - LT IAFP, Hart, George, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 7)
    - ST IAFP, Hollingsworth, William, SI, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 8)
    - LT IAFP, Hutchinson, Victoria, SI, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 9)
    - LT IAFP, Indictor, Norman, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 10)
    - ST IAFP, James, Estelle, SI, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 11)
    - LT IAFP, Kramer, Carol, SI, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 12)
    - ST IAFP, Kramer, Jonathan, SI, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 13)
    - LT IAFP, Lebra, Joyce C., 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 14)
    - LT IAFP, Lenz, Ralph, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 15)
    - ST IAFP, Maga, Joseph, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 16)
    - ST IAFP, Martin, Carol, SI, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 17)
    - ST IAFP, Moll, Edward O., NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 18)
    - ST IAFP, Nickum, James, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 19)
    - ST IAFP, Payer, Cheryl A., 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 20)
    - ST IAFP, Rodriguez, Eloy, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 21)
    - LT IAFP, Rosenthal, Raymond, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 22)
    - LT IAFP, Ryan, Joseph, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 23)
    - LT IAFP, Trabin, Tom, NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 352, Folder 24)
    - LT IAFP, Tyler, Forrest B., NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - LT IAFP, Wada, Yoshiko, Smithsonian, 1982-1983 (Box 353, Folder 2)
    - LT IAFP, Wilner, Gabriel M., NSF, 1982-1983 (Box 353, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, Requests for Information, 1982 (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, General, 1979-1980 (Box 353, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, Law on Funds, India, PL 480, 1979-1980 (Box 353, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, Fellows, 1978-1979 (Box 353, Folder 7)
    - IAFP Operations, Meeting to Discuss Fellowships (Box 353, Folder 8)
    - Programs in India, 1977 November 9 (Box 353, Folder 9)
    - IAFP, General, 1976-1977 (Box 353, Folder 10)
    - IAFP Operations, AIIS (American Institute of Indian Studies), Designated Representatives (Box 353, Folder 11)
    - AIIS to India, American Institute of Indian Studies, Manual of Procedures for AIIS Grantees (Box 389, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, Indo-American Fellowship Program, General Information, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, Visa Clearance Problems (Box 389, Folder 3)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Confidential material
    - IAFP, Wolinsky, Ira (Box 389, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, LT, Wirght, Carolyne L., S, 1976-1987 (Box 389, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, LT, Clymer, Kenton, S, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, ST, Coward, E. Walter, NSF, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, ST, Handelsman, Bruce D., SI, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 8)
    - IAFP, LT, Kowal, David, S, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 9)
    - IAFP, ST, Pacholczyk, Jozef M., S., 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 10)
    - IAFP, LT, Johnson, Rodney L., NSF, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 11)
    - IAFP, ST, Flanagan, Ted Benjamin, NSF, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 12)
    - IAFP, LT, Gold, Gerald, NSF, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 13)
    - IAFP, Dray, Tevian (Box 389, Folder 14)
    - IAFP, ST, Lopata, Helena Z., SI, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 15)
    - IAFP, LT, Fishman, Jonathan, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 16)
    - IAFP, LT, Mahr, Theodore A., S, 1986-1987 (Box 389, Folder 17)
    - IAFP, General Info, 1987-1988 (Box 389, Folder 18)
    - IAFP, ST, Baker, Victor, NSF, 1987-1988 (Box 389, Folder 19)
    - IAFP, LT, Clements, Clancy, SI, 1987-1988 (Box 389, Folder 20)
    - IAFP, ST, DeWeese, Devin S., SI, 1987-1988 (Box 389, Folder 21)
    - IAFP, LT, Horowitz, Joseph, NSF, 1987-1988 (Box 389, Folder 23)
    - IAFP, LT, Chittick, William C., SI, 1987-1988 (Box 389, Folder 23)
    - IAFP, ST, Evans, Peter B., NSF, 1987-1988 (Box 390, Folder 1)
    - IAFP, LT, Haddad, Jamey G., SI, 1987-1988 (Box 390, Folder 2)
    - IAFP, LT, McChesney, Robert D., SI, 1987-1988 (Box 390, Folder 3)
    - IAFP, LT, Manogue, Corinne, NSF, 1987-1988 (Box 390, Folder 4)
    - IAFP, ST, Mukhopadhyay, Carol C., NSF, 1987-1988 (Box 390, Folder 5)
    - IAFP, LT, Roopnarine, Jaipaul L., NSF, 1987-1988 (Box 390, Folder 6)
    - IAFP, LT, Sims, Eleanor G., SI, 1987-1988 (Box 390, Folder 7)
    - IAFP, ST, Steinmann, Linda K., SI, 1987-1988 (Box 390, Folder 8)